{
    "id": "db1910f623ec4a58af4259a5452ce395",
    "title": "Idioms Exercise",
    "questions": [
        {
            "question": "His parents bail him ............................... whenever he is in trouble.",
            "description": "To bail somebody out is to rescue them when they are in difficulty.",
            "answers": [
                "up",
                "off",
                "out"
            ],
            "correct": 2,
            "id": "68fdd9c4b5514a3791908403b0c8a9fe"
        },
        {
            "question": "We cannot sell things ................................... a loss.",
            "description": "To sell things at a loss is to sell at less than the cost.",
            "answers": [
                "with",
                "at",
                "for"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "fbf10075c280401c8ddab435d49adf9c"
        },
        {
            "question": "The new promotional campaign gave much ............................... for the buck.",
            "description": "Bang for the buck means value for the money spent.",
            "answers": [
                "bang",
                "bonanza",
                "booze"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "15e9997004ca4358b33fc0dcf615ccc4"
        },
        {
            "question": "Few people have the luxury of working ................................ hours these days.",
            "description": "Banker's hours means short work hours.",
            "answers": [
                "banker's",
                "baker's",
                "writer's"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "c8c7e0ae9091405ba72d70756fbd6cf5"
        },
        {
            "question": "He had no one to ..................................... him when he launched his business.",
            "description": "To bankroll somebody is to finance them.",
            "answers": [
                "bail",
                "bankroll",
                "back off"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "c738ae23e6df42ac9b4a92e9211ec024"
        },
        {
            "question": "He is a big ....................................... in his company.",
            "description": "All of these expressions refer to an important person.",
            "answers": [
                "wheel",
                "gun",
                "cheese",
                "All of the above"
            ],
            "correct": 3,
            "id": "b407e9c80e344206bcd3a664f0d8eced"
        },
        {
            "question": "If we had done our homework, we wouldn't have .................................. that deal.",
            "description": "To blow a deal is to ruin a business.",
            "answers": [
                "burst",
                "blown"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "b4e8a800898b483f87ac9f4d3b5864bf"
        },
        {
            "question": "When the ........................................... fell out of the property market, many builders had to cancel projects.",
            "description": "When the bottom falls out a collapse occurs and prices fall too much.",
            "answers": [
                "top",
                "bottom",
                "head"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "32e54f46c44047afa1842bd3ab18e014"
        },
        {
            "question": "Before investing in a company, you should examine its ........................................",
            "description": "The bottom line is the final figure on a balance sheet.",
            "answers": [
                "top line",
                "bottom line",
                "margin"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "b0750b3233e844b29e00bf9b98a599b6"
        },
        {
            "question": "It took us two years to break ...................................",
            "description": "A company breaks even when its expenses equal profits.",
            "answers": [
                "up",
                "even",
                "odd"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "dcf788dd2dc44348847ee11aa7af3e16"
        },
        {
            "question": "The large company is buying .................................... several small companies.",
            "description": "To buy out is to buy the ownership of something.",
            "answers": [
                "off",
                "out",
                "up"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "0f85ea39e422478694f75cb0e6133f52"
        },
        {
            "question": "The deal is almost fixed. Now we only have to sign on the …………………….. line.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "dotted",
                "blank",
                "raised"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "250afee9f8974edca5ede56951157a5d"
        }
    ]
}